<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="net.sourceforge.vice.feature"
      label="Versatile Commodore Emulator (VICE)"
      version="3.8.0.qualifier"
      provider-name="Torkild U. Resheim"
      plugin="net.sourceforge.vice"
      os="macosx"
      ws="cocoa"
      arch="aarch64,x86_64">

   <description url="https://vice-emu.sourceforge.io/index.html">
      VICE is an emulator for Commodore 8-bit computers.
   </description>

   <copyright>
      The VICE is copyrighted to: Pottendo, Marco van den Heuvel, Fabrizio Gennari, Groepaz, Errol Smith, Ingo Korb, Olaf Seibert, Marcus Sutton, Kajtar Zsolt, AreaScout, Bas Wassink, Michael C. Martin, Christopher Phillips, David Hogan, Empathic Qubit, Roberto Muscedere, June Tate-Gans, Pablo Roldan, Stefan Haubenthal, BSzili, Andreas Matthies, Daniel Kahlin, Benjamin &apos;BeRo&apos; Rosseaux, Ulrich Schulz, Thomas Giesel, Antti S. Lankila, Christian Vogelgsang, Dag Lem, Spiro Trikaliotis, Hannu Nuotio, Andreas Boose, Tibor Biczo, M. Kiesel, Andreas Dehmel, David Hansel, Markus Brenner, Thomas Bretz, Daniel Sladic, Andre Fachat, Ettore Perazzoli, Teemu Rantanen, Jouko Valta, Jarkko Sonninen, Mikkel Holm Olsen, Manuel Antonio Rodriguez Bas, Paul Dube, Czirkos Zoltan, Karai Csaba, Andrea Musuruane, Jesse Lee, Jarek Sobolewski, Michael Litvinov, Peter Krefting, Emir Akaydin.
   </copyright>

   <license url="https://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-3.0.html">
      VICE is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation; either version 2 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.

VICE is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the GNU General Public License for more details.
   </license>

   <plugin
         id="net.sourceforge.vice"
         version="0.0.0"/>

   <plugin
         id="net.sourceforge.vice.cocoa.macosx.x86_64"
         os="macosx"
         ws="cocoa"
         arch="x86_64"
         version="0.0.0"/>

   <plugin
         id="net.sourceforge.vice.cocoa.macosx.aarch64"
         os="macosx"
         ws="cocoa"
         arch="aarch64"
         version="0.0.0"/>

</feature>
